Prayer Line At The Mexico Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
Healing In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
CRUSADE IN PERU WITH T.B. JOSHUA
Claudia Esquivar
Mexico
I came here in a wheelchair because of an accident in which I twisted my ankle
and I was in so much pain.
It was pain that I had never experienced before so I was taken in an ambulance to hospital.
When I arrived at the hospital, the pain was so much, I felt like fainting.
They took x-rays and told me that I needed an operation
and put a plaster cast on my leg, which they said I would have to use for two and a half months.
At the beginning, the doctor said that she needed an operation.
They took some x-rays and found out that her ankle was broken.
The doctor decided to immobilise her leg and put it in a cast so she could not move it.
The doctor also told me that I should not walk with my injured leg, for two and a half months
because if I did, I would further injure myself; then, I would have to go for an operation.
Moreover, the doctors told me that after two and a half months, I would need therapy,
to be able to move and restore my leg back to its normal condition.
I was using a wheelchair. I could not do anything alone as someone had to always assist me -
to bathe me, dress me up and move me around. All the time, I was wheelchair-bound.
I had to take medication three times a day to dull the pain, despite the plaster cast on my leg.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I felt immense joy and peace.
I felt the presence of God and was assured within me that I was already healed.
At that moment, I stood up with confidence, giving glory and thanks to God
for using Prophet T.B. Joshua to heal me.
I stood up from the wheelchair and walked with confidence and great joy.
Little by little, I took some steps; then, I started walking normally.
She said that at the moment Prophet T.B. Joshua touched her,
she felt a lot of peace inside her.
With boldness - she was so confident that God was going to heal her -
she stood up and started walking and jumping
because the Lord had just healed her at that moment.
After my healing, my life has changed - I am free.
I have been free since that moment when the pain left me and I was able to stand up.
For me, everyday is a day to glorify and give thanks to God for what He has done in my life.
I believed in God, I trusted in Him; if He did it for me, He can do it for you.
You have to have faith;
you have to declare and take possession of your healing because it is there for you.
God is alive; He is the same yesterday and today. He wants to manifest Himself in all of us.
Ever since I received my freedom, I can do everything!
I can walk and run. I don't need any therapy and no longer feel pain even in cold weather.
I do not feel any pain and when the doctors saw my x-rays, they could hardly believe it!
They saw the x-rays of both before and after my healing and the doctors were very shocked.
Amen. Praise the Lord!
Testimony From The Mexico Crusade
With Prophet T.B. Joshua 2015